Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Departmental Files, 1940-1960; Series I
  - 1956-1957
    - World Health Organization
      - National Citizen's Committee for, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3027)
    - World Health Organization, 1956-1957 (Box 287, Folder 3028-3029)
      - Pan American Sanitary Bureau, 1956-1957 (Box 288, Folder 3030)
    - National Conference for Cooperation in Health Education, 1956-1957 (Box 288, Folder 3031)
    - Association for Retarded Children in Greater New Haven, 1956-1957 (Box 288, Folder 3032)
    - Gaylord Farm Sanatorium, 1956-1957 (Box 288, Folder 3033-3036)
  - 1957-1958
    - A General, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3037-3039)
    - B General, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3040)
    - Bliss, Susan, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3041)
    - Blumenthal, Andre, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3042)
    - Clifford W. Beers lecture, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3043)
    - C General, 1957-1958 (Box 289, Folder 3044-3045)
    - C General, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3046)
    - Canada, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3047)
    - D General, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3048)
    - E General, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3049)
    - England, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3050)
      - Dr. Hugh Paul, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3051)
    - Dr. J.N. Morris, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3052)
    - F General, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3053)
    - Fellowships, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3054)
    - Films, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3055)
    - G General, 1957-1958 (Box 290, Folder 3056)
    - H General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3057)
    - Hawaii, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3058)
    - I General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3059-3061)
    - J General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3062)
    - K General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3063)
    - L General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3064)
    - M General, 1957-1958 (Box 291, Folder 3065)
    - N General, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3066-3068)
    - New Canaan, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3069)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3070)
    - O General, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3071)
    - P General, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3072-3073)
    - R General, 1957-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3074)
    - S General, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3075)
    - T General, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3076)
    - U General, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3077)
    - Universities and colleges other than Yale and ASPH, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3078)
    - V General, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3079)
    - W General, 1957-1958 (Box 293, Folder 3080)
    - Waterbury, City of: newspaper clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3081)
    - Winslow, Charles Edward A., 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3082)
    - Winslow Lecture, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3083)
    - Y General, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3084)
    - Yale University: general, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3085-3086)
    - Anatomy, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3087)
    - Applied Physiology, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3088)
    - History of Medicine, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3089)
    - Law, School of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3090)
    - Nursing, School of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3091)
    - Political Science, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3092)
    - Psychiatry, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3093)
    - Sociology, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3094)
    - University Health, Department of, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3095)
    - Yale University, President, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3096)
    - Yale University, Secretary, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3097)
    - Yale University, Treasurer, 1957-1958 (Box 294, Folder 3098)
    - Yale University, Provost, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3099)
    - Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3100)
    - Recommendations for appointment, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3101)
    - Dean, School of Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3102)
    - Association Dean, School of Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3103)
      - Postgraduate education, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3104)
    - Registrar, School of Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3105-3107)
    - Committee on Admissions, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3108)
    - Business Manager, Medical School, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3109)
    - Executive Secretary, School of Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3110)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1957-1958 (Box 295, Folder 3111)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3112)
    - Executive Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3113)
    - Medical Library and Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3114)
    - Dean, Graduate School, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3115)
    - Assistant Dean, Graduate School, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3116)
    - Registrar, Graduate School, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3117)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3118)
    - Grace-New Haven community Hospital, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3119)
    - Department of Public Health: general, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3120-3121)
    - Hospital Administration Section, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3122)
    - Occupational Health, 1957-1958 (Box 296, Folder 3123)
    - Cancer Control Section, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3124)
    - Secretarial staff, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3125)
    - Alumni, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3126)
    - Field trips, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3127)
    - Candidates for jobs, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3128)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3129)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3130-3131)
    - Articles and publications, 1957-1958 (Box 297, Folder 3132)
    - Correspondence regarding speaking engagements, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3133)
    - Ladies Aid, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3134)
    - Nathan Smith Club, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3135)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3136)
    - American Cancer Society, 1958 (Box 298, Folder 3137)
      - Connecticut Division, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3138)
      - Other divisions, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3139)
    - American Dental Association, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3140)
    - American Heart Association, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3141)
      - Connecticut Chapter, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3142)
      - New Haven Chapter, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3143)
    - American Medical Association, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3144)
    - American Public Health Association
      - General, 1957-1958 (Box 298, Folder 3145-3147)
      - Accreditation, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3148)
      - Committee on Eligibility, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3149)
      - Annual meeting, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3150)
      - American Journal of Public Health, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3151)
      - Mental Health Section, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3152)
      - Southern Branch, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3153)
    - Professional Examination Service: monthly reports, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3154)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Governing Council, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3155)
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3156)
    - American Red Cross, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3157)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3158)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3159-3161)
      - Quinnipiac Council, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3162)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1957-1958 (Box 299, Folder 3163)
    - National Budget Committee, 1957 (Box 300, Folder 3166)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3167)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3168)
    - Connecticut Public Health Nursing, 1958 (Box 300, Folder 3169)
    - Connecticut Regional Blood Program, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3170)
    - Connecticut Association for Mental Health, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3171-3172)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3173)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3174)
    - Connecticut State Medical Journal, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3175)
    - New Haven Medical Association, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3176)
    - Connecticut, State of
      - General, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3177)
      - Commission on Alcoholism, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3178)
      - Department of Education, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3179)
      - Governor, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3180)
      - Tuberculosis Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 300, Folder 3181)
      - Lane School Board of Directors, 1957-1958 (Box 301, Folder 3182-3183)
      - Long Lane School, Governor"s Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 301, Folder 3184)
    - Southbury Training School, 1957-1958 (Box 301, Folder 3185)
    - Connecticut, State of
      - Department of Health, 1957-1958 (Box 301, Folder 3186-3187)
      - Health Department, 1957-1958 (Box 301, Folder 3188)
      - Health Department, 1957-1958 (Box 302, Folder 3189-3190)
    - Commissioner of Health, 1957-1958 (Box 302, Folder 3191)
    - Directors of Health, 1957-1958 (Box 302, Folder 3192)
    - Public Health Council, 1957-1958 (Box 302, Folder 3193)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1957-1958 (Box 302, Folder 3194)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1957-1958 (Box 303, Folder 3195-3196)
    - Dental Clinic, Society of New Haven, 1957-1958 (Box 303, Folder 3197)
    - Health Departments: local, state, national, 1958, 1957 (Box 303, Folder 3198-3201)
    - New York State Health Department, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3202)
    - New York City Health Department, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3203)
    - Health Information Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3204)
    - Human Relations Area Files, Incorporated, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3205)
    - Publishers, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3209)
    - National Association for Mental Health, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3210)
    - National Citizen"s Committee on Educational Television, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3211)
    - National Education Association, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3212)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3213)
      - New Haven, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3214)
    - National Health Council, 1957-1958 (Box 304, Folder 3215-3216)
    - National Health Council, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3217-3218)
    - National League for Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3219)
    - Interrogation Committees on Tuberculosis Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3220)
    - National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Services, Incorporated, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3221)
    - National Society for Crippled Children and Adults, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3222-3223)
    - National Research Council, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3224)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 305, Folder 3225)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 306, Folder 3226)
    - National Safety Council, 1957-1958 (Box 306, Folder 3227)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1957-1958 (Box 306, Folder 3228)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1957-1958 (Box 306, Folder 3229-3230)
    - Special Project: Prevention of Blindness and Conservation of Vision, 1957-1958 (Box 306, Folder 3231)
    - New York Committee on Children's Teeth, 1957 (Box 306, Folder 3232)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1957-1958 (Box 307, Folder 3233-3238)
    - New Haven Tuberculosis and Health Association, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3239)
    - New England Health Institute, 1958 (Box 308, Folder 3240)
    - Association for Retarded Children in Greater New Haven (Guidance Center), 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3241)
    - New Haven Army Advisory Committee, 1957 (Box 308, Folder 3242)
    - New Haven, City of
      - General, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3243)
      - Mayor's office, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3244)
    - New Haven Rehabilitation Center, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3245)
    - Citizen"s Action Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3246)
    - Tuberculosis Advisory Commission of Greater New Haven, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3247)
    - Tuberculosis Survey: New Haven schools, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3248)
    - New Haven, City of: Department of Health, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3249)
    - Minutes of meeting, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3250)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3251)
    - Health Division: Council of Social Agencies, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3252)
    - New Haven Junior League, 1957 (Box 308, Folder 3253)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3254)
    - Schools of Public Health, Association of, 1957-1958 (Box 308, Folder 3256)
    - Schools of Public Health, Association of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3257-3259)
    - California, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3260)
    - Columbia University, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3261)
    - Harvard University, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3262)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3263)
    - Michigan, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3264)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3265)
    - Montreal, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3266)
    - North Carolina, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3267)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1957-1958 (Box 309, Folder 3268)
    - Puerto Rico, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3269)
    - Tulane University of Louisiana, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3270)
    - Society of Public Health, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3271)
    - United States Government: general, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3272)
    - United States Armed Forces, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3273)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3274)
    - United States Census Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3275)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3276)
    - President's Council on Youth Fitness, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3277)
    - United States Department of Health Education and Welfare: general, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3278-3280)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1957-1958 (Box 310, Folder 3281)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1957-1958 (Box 311, Folder 3282-3285)
      - Cancer Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 311, Folder 3286)
      - Heart Association, 1957-1958 (Box 311, Folder 3287)
      - International Health, Division of, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3288)
      - Mental Health Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3289)
      - State Services, Division of, 1957 (Box 312, Folder 3290)
    - Veterans' Administration: general, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3291)
    - Veterans' Administration Hospital: West Haven, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3292)
    - World Health Organization
      - General, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3293-3294)
      - National Citizens' Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3295)
    - World Health Organization, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3296)
    - National Conference for Cooperation in Health Education, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3297)
    - Bernice P. Bishop Museum, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3298)
    - Gaylord Farm Sanatorium, 1957-1958 (Box 312, Folder 3299-3300)
    - Gaylord Farm Sanatorium, 1957-1958 (Box 313, Folder 3301-3304)
    - Bridgeport Health Department and Survey, 1957-1958 (Box 313, Folder 3305)
    - Gaylord Farm Development Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 313, Folder 3306)
  - 1958-1959
    - A General, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3307-3309)
    - B General, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3310)
    - Bliss, Susan, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3311)
    - Blumenthal, Andre, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3312)
    - Bunnell, Mrs. Sterling, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3313)
    - C General, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3314-3315)
    - Canada, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3316)
    - D General, 1958-1959 (Box 314, Folder 3317)
    - E General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3318)
    - England, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3319)
      - Dr. Hugh Paul, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3320)
    - F General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3321)
    - Fellowships, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3322)
    - Films, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3323)
    - G General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3324)
    - H General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3325)
    - Hawaii, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3326)
    - I General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3327)
    - J General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3328)
    - K General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3329)
    - L General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3330)
    - M General, 1958-1959 (Box 315, Folder 3331)
    - N General, 1958-1959 (Box 316, Folder 3332-3334)
    - New Canaan, 1958-1959 (Box 316, Folder 3335)
    - O General, 1958-1959 (Box 316, Folder 3336-3337)
    - P General, 1958-1959 (Box 316, Folder 3338)
    - R General, 1958-1959 (Box 316, Folder 3339)
    - S General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3340)
    - St. Louis, Missouri: progress report on survey, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3341)
    - Shindell, Dr. Sidney, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3342)
    - T General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3343)
    - U General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3344)
    - V General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3345)
    - Universities and colleges other than Yale and Association of School and Public Health, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3346)
    - W General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3347)
    - Winslow, Charles Edward A., 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3348)
    - Winslow Lecture, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3349)
    - Winslow, Mrs. C.E.A., 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3350)
    - Winslow Award Committee, 1958 (Box 317, Folder 3351)
    - Y General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3352)
    - Z General, 1958-1959 (Box 317, Folder 3353)
    - Yale University: general, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3354-3355)
    - Yale-in-China (New Asia College), 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3356)
    - Retired Yale faculty, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3357)
    - Department of Applied Physiology (Alcohol Studies), 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3358)
    - Department of the History of Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3359)
    - School of Law, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3360)
    - School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3361)
    - Schorske, Florence: Dean, School of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3362)
    - Department of Political Science, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3363)
    - Graduates Club, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3364)
    - Department of Psychiatry, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3365)
    - Department of Sociology, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3366)
    - Department of University Health, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3367)
    - President, Yale University, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3368)
    - Secretary, Yale University, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3369)
    - Treasurer, Yale University, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3370)
    - Provost, Yale University, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3371)
    - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3372)
    - Dean, School of Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 318, Folder 3373-3374)
    - Assistant Dean: School of Medicine (Admissions), 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3375)
    - Assistant Dean: School of Medicine (Postgraduate Education), 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3376)
    - Dr. John R. Paul, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3377)
    - Registrar: School of Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3378)
    - Admissions, Committee on, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3379)
    - Student Affairs, Committee on, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3380)
    - Business Manager: Medical School, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3381)
    - Medical School: general, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3382)
    - Executive Secretary: School of Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3383)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3384-3385)
    - Executive Committee: Board of Permanent Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3386)
    - Medical Library, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3387)
    - Dean: Graduate School, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3388)
    - Assistant Dean: Graduate School, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3389)
    - Graduate School: general (Box 319, Folder 3390)
    - Registrar: Graduate School, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3391)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1958-1959 (Box 319, Folder 3392)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3393)
      - Health Education Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3394)
    - Public Health, Department of: general, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3395-3396)
    - Secretarial staff, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3397)
    - Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3398)
    - Alumni, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3399)
    - Field trips, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3400)
    - Student loans, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3401)
    - Candidates for jobs, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3402)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1958-1959 (Box 320, Folder 3403)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3404-3405)
    - Ladies Aid, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3407)
    - The Nathan Smith Club, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3408)
    - Shriver, Margaret C., 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3409)
    - Sohler, Katherine B., 1957-1958 (Box 321, Folder 3410)
    - Herrington, Dr. Lovic, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3411)
    - Pelletier, Robert, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3412)
    - Miguel Enrique Bustamante, 1958-1959 (Box 321, Folder 3413)
    - Edward Ludger Raymond, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3413A)
    - Pearson, Richard John C., 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3414)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3415)
    - American Cancer Society: national office, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3416)
    - American Cancer Society: Connecticut Division, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3417)
    - American Heart Association, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3418)
      - Connecticut Chapter, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3419)
      - New Haven Chapter, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3420)
    - American Medical Association, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3421)
    - American Public Health Association, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3422-3424)
      - Accreditation, 1959 (Box 322, Folder 3425)
      - Annual meeting, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3426)
      - American Journal of Public Health, 1958-1959 (Box 322, Folder 3427)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3428)
      - Committee on Affiliated Societies and Regional Branches, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3429)
      - Mental Health Section, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3430)
      - Albert Lasker Awards, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3431)
      - Professional Examination Service monthly reports, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3432)
      - Governing Council, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3433)
    - American Public Health Association, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3434-3435)
    - American Red Cross, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3436)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3437)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3438)
      - Quinnipiac Council, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3439)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1958-1959 (Box 323, Folder 3440)
    - National Budget Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3442)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3443-3444)
    - Connecticut League of Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3445)
    - Occupational Therapy: Connecticut Association, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3446)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3447)
    - Connecticut Public Health Nursing Association, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3448)
    - Connecticut Regional Blood Program, 1958-1959 (Box 324, Folder 3449)
    - Connecticut Association for Mental Health, 1958-1959 (Box 325, Folder 3450-3451)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1958-1959 (Box 325, Folder 3452)
    - Connecticut state Medical Society, 1958-1959 (Box 325, Folder 3453)